sakura-house.com 2017-06-12

# SAKURA HOUSE - Privacy policy

Since its establishment in 1992, Sakura House Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as “the Company”) has offered rental accommodation such as guest houses and apartments at a reasonable price to customers from over 100 different countries each year.  
This website (hereinafter referred to as “this Website”) acquires information (hereinafter referred to as “Personal Information”) required for contacts and transactions during procedures including reservations and inquiries, such as the customer’s name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address.  
The Company works to protect privacy and strictly manages the Personal Information of customers while complying with the Personal Information Protection Act, as well as other related laws, ordinances, and standards.  
All Personal Information provided to the Company will not be provided or submitted to a third party, excluding when the customer’s agreement has been obtained or there is a valid reason.

The Personal Information of customers shall be appropriately acquired, used and provided within the scope of the Company’s business such as room reservations, inquiries, and sending information about various events and promotional campaigns. If the Personal Information will be used for purposes other than those clearly stated when the customer provides the Personal Information, the customer shall be contacted immediately regarding that purpose.

#### Provision to third parties

As a rule, Personal Information provided by the customer shall not be disclosed, provided, or transferred to a third party, except in the following cases.   
・When required to carry out the business of the Company’s group companies, including information about various events and promotional campaigns, contact about products and services, etc.   
・When required to carry out business for the Company’s subcontracting  
・When agreement has been obtained from the customer

However, Personal Information may be disclosed or provided without obtaining agreement from the customer in the following cases.   
・If ordered to disclose Personal Information for legal reasons  
・If it is impossible to obtain agreement from the customer and there is danger of damage to the life, health, or assets of the customer or a third party  
・If required to do so for serious and urgent reasons related to the customer, the Company, or a third party

#### The usage of cookies

Some pages use cookies in order to make it possible to view this Website in a smooth fashion. When the customer visits this Website again, cookies are used to confirm whether the computer has been used to visit this Website previously and to simplify the entering of information into forms.  
It is possible to set the browser you use to not accept cookies. However, if cookies are disabled by the customer, some functions of this Website cannot be used.

Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) is used to make it easier for customers to use this Website by encrypting transmitted information. It is not used to identify the specific Personal Information of a customer. The inquiry forms on this Website supports SSL.  
Names, e-mail addresses, and other Personal Information entered by the customer is protected and safely transmitted to the Company.

#### Management of subcontractors

When entrusting the processing of Personal Information to a third party, the Company inspects whether or not the subcontractor is protecting Personal Information in a safe manner and enters into a nondisclosure agreement with the subcontractor.

#### Revisions to this Privacy Policy

When revisions have been made to this Privacy Policy, they will be announced on the Site. Please confirm the latest information on the Site.
